trycaviar.com 2014-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Caviar

The Caviar privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to inform you on how we collect, use, and disclose any personally identifiable information you submit to us through our Website (www.trycaviar.com) Caviar, a subsidiary of Delaware corporation Munch On Me, Inc., the provider of the Website (referred to as "us" or "we"), is committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the "User" or "End User") and how we use that information. By accessing and using Caviar, you acknowledge that you have read and understand our privacy policy. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us. 

### Information Collected

Personally Identifiable Information (PII). Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific End User. This includes our registration page which collects your name, valid email address, and password of your choice. Caviar also has Facebook Connect, which may access information that includes your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, and any other information you share with everyone. Through Facebook, we may also contact you directly through that email.Upon entering your account page, you may have the option to specify your age, gender, and demographic information. When you purchase a Deal, you will need to submit your credit card or other payment information so that our service providers can process your payment for the Deal. We collect any voluntarily provided information, while you are on the site. This includes reviews, submissions, subscriptions, referrals or any actions performed on the website. 

### Release of Personally Identifiable Information

We do not release, sell, or expose any Personally Identifiable Information that you provide us to third parties for marketing purposes, unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy. However, we may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with our Partners, Affiliates, and Advertisers to better improve the Caviar product and user experience. 

We may provide your Personal Information to third-parties service providers to improve communication between our users and merchants. This may include sending email, tracking data, processing payments (including credit card payments, reward points), and providing customer service. We require that our third parties commit to not using such information except as necessary to provide their product or services. 

All data and statistical information collected by Caviar will be used and analyzed internally to improve our product. 

### Data Tracking

To collect data and track our users, we store cookies onto your computer. The cookie contains information about the user as well as tracks the pages you have clicked or visited. All of this information is considered Non Personally Identifiable Information. The purpose of this is to improve our customization and help us create a more user-friendly experience for all visitors. Some browsers may have the option under settings to prevent cookie tracking. 

The cookies we collect are for our website and webpages only. Once you leave Caviar and visit a third party platform or website, we no longer have control or access to those cookies. 

### User Choice on Collecting Information

We may send weekly promotional and administrative emails, account information, and request inquiries. If you no longer want to be notified, you may at any time "opt-out" of our promotional communications by unsubscribing to our email. Please email support@trycaviar.com if you need additional help. 

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

If the privacy policy changes, it will affect this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we believe that you are aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. We may notify you through email as well. 

### Security

Your personal information is extremely important to us. Your information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel have access to. Credit card information is encrypted. Promotional and referral codes are random alphanumeric sequences that are encrypted. In addition to our precautions, it is important that you do not share your password with anyone. Although we try our best to protect your information, we cannot completely eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information. 

Last updated on 04 October 2013.
